<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MUWS 2023 - The 2nd International Workshop on Multimodal Human Understanding for the Web and Social Media on MUWS 2023</title>
    <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MUWS 2023 - The 2nd International Workshop on Multimodal Human Understanding for the Web and Social Media on MUWS 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://muws-workshop.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers</title>
      <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muws-workshop.github.io/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Multimodal human understanding and analysis is an emerging research area that cuts through several disciplines like Computer Vision, Natural Language Processing (NLP), Speech Processing, Human-Computer Interaction, and Multimedia. Several multimodal learning techniques have recently shown the benefit of combining multiple modalities in image-text, audio-visual and video representation learning and various downstream multimodal tasks. At the core, these methods focus on modelling the modalities and their complex interactions by using large amounts of data, different loss functions and deep neural network architectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MUWS 2022 @ The Web Conf 2022</title>
      <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/previous/2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muws-workshop.github.io/previous/2022/</guid>
      <description>The 1st International Workshop on Multimodal Understanding for the Web and Social Media (MUWS), co-located with The WebConf (WWW) 2022
Participation: Online
Workshop Date: April 26, 2022
Workshop Proceedings: https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3487553.3524873
Workshop Recordings Program 14:00 - 14:05 - Welcome session
14:05 - 14:50 - Keynote talk by Ichiro Ide &amp;ldquo;Tailoring Applications to Users Through Multi-modal Understanding&amp;rdquo;
Prof. Ichiro Ide received his BEng, MEng, and PhD from The University of Tokyo in 1994, 1996, and 2000, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organization</title>
      <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muws-workshop.github.io/organization/</guid>
      <description>Organizing Committee Gullal S. Cheema L3S Research Center, Leibniz University Hannover, Germany
Website
Sherzod Hakimov University of Potsdam, Germany
Website
Marc A. Kastner Kyoto University, Japan
Website
Noa Garcia Osaka University, Japan
Website
Programme Committee Eric Müller-Budack, TIB &amp;ndash; Leibniz Information Centre for Science and Technology, Germany Christian Otto, L3S Research Center, Germany Sina Zarrieß, Bielefeld University, Germany Malihe Alikhani, University of Pittsburgh, USA Tuomo Hiippala, University of Helsinki, Finland Chihaya Matsuhira, Nagoya University, Japan Nils Murrugarra-Llerena, Snap Inc, USA Letitia Parcalabescu, University of Heidelberg, Germany Arka Ujjal Dey, Computer Vision Center, Spain Ricardo Marcacini, University of Sao Paulo, Brazil Sandro Pezzelle, University of Amsterdam, Netherlands Raffaella Bernardi, University of Trento, Italy </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muws-workshop.github.io/program/</guid>
      <description>To be announced&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission</title>
      <link>https://muws-workshop.github.io/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muws-workshop.github.io/submission/</guid>
      <description>Submission Instructions TBD
Submission Page Submission Page: TBD Important datess Submission deadline: August 18th, 2023 Paper notification: September 15th, 2023 Workshop date: October 22nd, 2023 Contact If you have any problems or questions, please contact us via e-mail at: TBD</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
